This program is suitable
for viewers ages 15 and up.
[Goblin: The Lonely and Great God]
Subtitles by DramaFever
若灵魂附在某人的旧物
或沾了血的物件上
便会成为鬼怪
上过无数战场 染过鲜血的长剑
沾染上了主人的血更甚
If a spirit inhabits an object that has
the touch or the blood of a human on it
the spirit becomes a goblin.
唯有鬼怪的新娘 才可拔出此剑
拔出剑之后 一切归于无 便可安息
And this was a sword
from a battlefield
with the blood of thousands on it
with even its own owner's blood on
it, so it was only to be expected.
这是恶毒的神谕
而以不死之身重生的鬼怪
在这世上亦有亦无
And only the bride of the goblin will
be able to pull out that sword.
此刻也在某...
笑什么 死丫头
And when the sword is pulled out
he will become nothing
once more, and rest in peace.
此刻 也可能在某处寻找着新娘
而那个新娘... 就是我
你是想这么说的吗
别看我现在这样
年轻时可是俘获了不少男人的心
下次来时若我不在了 你可别吃惊
Of course, this is a cruel
deal for the goblin.
真是羡慕啊
The goblin, which woke up
to realize that it is immortal
我真是老糊涂了
跟你这个未婚妈妈炫耀这些
is everywhere and nowhere in
this world at the same time
and even now, nobody
knows where he may be...
真坏
菠菜 白菜都给你算便宜了
我还坏
Why the hell are you laughing, girl?
是抛弃你的那个混蛋坏才是
Are you about to tell me, "He's still
looking for his bride, and it's me"?
那倒是
不过这个故事好伤感
Even though I look like this now, I had
hordes of men following me in my prime!
有何伤感的
是一个浪漫而怨毒的诅咒
Don't come back next time
only to be surprised to find me gone.
为求死而寻找新娘
Wow, I'm so jealous.
神真坏
I'm just getting old.
神原本就不是好惹的
That's not something for me to
brag about in front of you, though.
自私 善妒
Hey, that's not nice!
唯我独尊
No, I'm not! I give you discounts
on spinach and cabbage!
和某人真像
The bastard who left you behind
and ran off is the not nice one here.
我走了 祝您生意兴隆
You do have a point.
下次来 您也一定要在哦
But you know, that story is too sad.
Ha, sure.
It's really a romantic sort of curse.
危在旦夕时
I mean, he has to find
his bride in order to die.
你要虔诚祷告
God is cruel.
God has always been cruel.
可能某位心慈的神
And he's selfish and jealous too.
会听到你的祷告
God only cares about himself.
He's just like another
guy we know, huh?
Well, I'll be going now.
I hope you sell a lot.
And you'd better be
here next time too, okay?
换做是我 不会这么做
你若现在离开家
When you're in a position in which
your life is flashing before your eyes
就会过上比现在更糟糕的生活
可能会再也见不到你妈妈
pray for mercy
with all your heart.
你是谁
韩国人吗
一言难尽
Because a god with a soft spot
may be listening to you.
现在该你了
逐字逐句地说清楚
[PARIS, 1968]
告诉他 既然领养了我
你便是我的父亲
所以 你该好好抚养我
去求你妈妈 让她帮你
告诉她你的痛苦
你在胡说八道什么
让开
提醒你一句 那样割脉只能废了手臂却死不了
你是谁
看着他 逐字逐句地说
I wouldn't recommend doing that.
能做到吗
要是被打死了怎么办
If you run away from home now, you'll
live with worse people than that.
你负责吗
所以我帮你弄断了他的肋骨
And you'll never see
your mother again.
Who the hell are you?
Are you Korean?
你个混蛋...
I'm a more complicated person
than you'd think.
It's your turn now.
Go and tell him clearly
"You've adopted me, so you're my father.
So you have to raise me well."
这是便当
等谈完了上学去
第17道数学题答案不是2 而是4
And ask your mother for help too.
And tell her you're in pain.
那道题不能错
你到底是谁
What kind of bull are you spouting?
Get the hell out of my way!
And slitting your wrist like
that won't kill you
but it'll render your hand
useless, so be aware of that.
Who are you?
Don't avoid his gaze
and speak clearly.
Can you do that?
And what if he beats me to death?
Will you take responsibility?
That's why I broke his rib for you.
You little bastard!
他是水 是火 是风
是光明 是黑暗
That's lunch for you.
也曾是...
Go to school
after you're done talking to him.
The answer for number 17
on the math quiz isn't 2. It's 4.
You got that question wrong, so...
Who... are you, really?
人类
He's water, wind, and fire.
Light and darkness.
And at one time...
百姓称他为神
he was human.
闯过血雨腥风 杀敌无数
当得起武神二字
His subjects called him "God."
He cut down his foes
covered in crimson blood.
And he was a military man
through and through.
金信将军万岁...
万岁...
将军万岁...
打开城门
金信将军 凯旋
金信卸下戎装
- Hooray!
大胆 竟敢出言不逊
正七品别将竟敢对上将军...
- Hooray for the general!
明君的叛臣金信 卸下戎装
竟敢...
好
等着
Step aside! It's the great
General Kim Shin!
Kim Shin will take off his armor
and heed the king's royal decree.
可以了吗
逆臣金信
I dare you to say
that again, punk!
弃剑 跪下领旨
我非割下你的舌头...
How dare some political
lackey like you oppose...
何来的逆臣 疯了不成
The criminal Kim Shin will
take off his armor and...
失心疯不成
How dare you!
I heard you loud and clear.
Wait there.
将军
逆臣 金信
弃剑跪下...
本将军要见殿下 让开
Happy now?
罪臣金信...
Criminal Kim Shin, put down your
sword and get on your knees
挡我者死
让开
and heed the king's royal decree.
I'll pull that rotten tongue
of yours right out!
"Criminal Kim Shin"?
Are you out of your damn mind?
Are you insane?
救命啊
General.
Criminal Kim Shin, put down your
sword and get on your knees...
救命啊
你们这帮家伙
I'm going to see the king.
Get out of my way.
以主君之名已战了3天3夜
- Criminal Kim Shin...
- If you don't move, you'll surely die.
好不容易才从人间地狱活着回来
Step aside.
可是你们... 你们竟敢...
打开城门
守在他们身边
我去去就来
You bastards!
These men fought
for three straight nights!
They were just on their way
back from that hell!
So how dare you...
how dare you bastards!
Open the castle gates!
Stay here and watch over the men.
I'll be right back.
百姓之上是王
王之上是神
据说那神就是指金信
他打了无数胜仗 蛊惑了百姓
他的权势再三嘲弄王室
请以国法严加惩处
他
虽能看清敌人的刀刃
They say that he's like a king among
the people and regarded as a god.
但没能看出年轻君王对自己的嫉妒和恐惧
And his name is Kim Shin.
那是 指向自己的最锋利的刀刃
That man's endless ascension to power
is making the citizens rise up
可惜他没能看清
and his power makes a mockery
of the royal family's authority.
So please, issue him the harshest
punishment you can under the law.
真要做到如此地步吗
所以不要再过来
He was able to see the blades
of his opponents quite well
停下
不管那是什么 都停下
but he'd been blind to the young
king's fear and jealousy toward him.
停在那里 死于逆贼之名吧
那么除了你之外 可以放过所有人
但是 如果再往前走一步
And he was unaware of the fact
你每迈出一步 每一个眼神
that the king's jealousy and fear were
sharper than any blade he'd known.
我都会杀了所有人铺在你的脚下
走吧 将军
我没关系
So he's really going this far?
Don't step any closer.
我...
Stop right there.
Stop all of it.
娘娘 我...
我知道
Stop right there and die.
If you do, I'll spare everyone else.
我真的全都知道
But if you take even one
more step toward me
如果这就是我的结局
那么这也是我的命运
I'll kill everyone in front of you
and lay their corpses at your feet.
所以你走吧
不要停下
去殿下那儿 将军
Go, General.
I'm all right.
I...
Your Highness, I...
I know.
I know everything.
And if this is the end for me,
then such is my fate.
这是谋反
满门抄斩 一个不留 这是御命
So please, go.
Don't stop, and keep
walking toward the king.
Don't spare her
or anyone related to her!
This is my command!
住手
还愣着干什么 让罪人跪下
将军
殿下 您这是为何
就不怕天谴吗
老天什么时候站在你们那边了
Stop!
罪人凶狠的眼神令御心慌乱
What are you doing?
Bring the criminal to his knees!
斩立决
这不关你事
General!
将军 将军 将军 将军
Your Highness!
How could you do this?
我想拜托你来结束我的性命
Have you no fear of the heavens?
It's not like the heavens
have ever taken your side.
Having that sinner's gaze
upon us is making me dizzy.
Strike him down now!
遵将军之命
This doesn't concern you.
General! General!
I want to make
a final request of you.
请您原谅
小的随后就来
To think that such a day would come.
任何人都不许替逆贼收尸
Forgive me, sir.
弃尸荒野任由猛禽野兽啃食
I'll be right behind you, sir.
他也就值给禽兽果腹
这是御命
Nobody may retrieve
this criminal's body.
Leave it out on the fields to be
consumed by wild animals!
Such is the only fitting punishment
for a criminal such as him.
This is a royal decree!
将军 一路走好
将军
我们的将军
好可怜
我们的将军好可怜...
将军...
不要求任何人
- Please have mercy, God!
- Please, spare him!
神不会听的
一日之中阳光最明媚的午时
他死于自己保护的主君的刀下
Don't pray to anyone or anything.
Because the gods aren't listening.
And on that clear,
sunny afternoon...
he died by the very
blade that he'd wielded.
[GOBLIN: THE LONELY AND GREAT GOD]
[SEOUL, 1998]
这种疯子
长眼睛来喘气的吗
找死...
你这小子
是什么东西
野猪
什么
你撞到了野猪
Ow, damn it!
You crazy bastard!
Are your eyes only there
for decoration?
You have a death... wish...
Hey, what's with you, bastard?
你没事吧
要不要帮你报警
A wild boar.
我撞到了野猪
What?
就是说...
野猪突然间窜出来
野...野猪 在江南正中心
You struck a wild boar
with your car.
那...那里
喂 是119吧
这里是驿三十字路口
后备箱里有个女人好像已经死了
不知道 现在一动不动
具体情况不知道
Are you all right, sir?
Do you want me to call the authorities?
究竟是因为交通事故 还是...
具体的不知道 请快点来看看
I just hit a wild boar, you see...
我怎么...
so, um, a wild boar
came out of nowhere!
-这里是驿三十字路口人行道
-我怎么会在那里
黄美英 25岁
A wild boar?
In the middle of Gangnam?
癸丑年 丁巳月 乙巳日 辰时出生
戊寅年 乙卯月 己卯日 八时三十二分死亡
It's... it's a person!
Oh my gosh, what do we do?
Hello? This is 911, right?
死因 窒息致死
I'm at the Yeoksang
four-way intersection.
There's a woman in the trunk of
a car here! I think she may be dead.
I'm not sure.
She's not moving. Yes.
是你本人吧
I'm not sure about that. I just happened
to come across this car accident...
I'm not sure what's going on.
You should hurry and come.
Yes.
Why am I...
why am I there?
Hwang Mi Young.
25 years old.
Born in the year of the ox
on March 1st.
Time of death is 08:32 on Friday.
That's the information
I have on the deceased.
喝吧 会让你忘掉今生的记忆
That's you, right?
如果不喝
会怎样
会后悔没有喝下去
不管是什么样的后悔
愿你都能留在今生
Drink it. It'll make you forget about
what happened to you in this life.
What happens if I don't drink this?
You'll come to regret it.
I hope that you will leave your
regrets behind with this life.
鬼怪
地狱使者
A goblin?
A god of death?
That's quite a vulgar
disguise he has on.
Your Lordship!
It's been 20 years
since I've last seen you.
Have you been well for
all those years, sir?
Have you been well?
Well, I've aged quite a bit, sir.
But you're looking
as brilliant as ever.
He doesn't look that cool to me.
You punk!
This is my grandson.
The one that I've told you about.
Greet him properly.
Who is this guy?
So you're Duk Hwa.
I'm someone who'll be your uncle, your
brother, your son, then your grandson.
Pleased to make your acquaintance.
What does that even mean?
You seem weirder and weirder
by the minute, Mister.
You brat!
Oh, I offer my deepest apologies, sir.
He's an only child
and was quite spoiled, you see.
But you...
Me? What about me?
There was a boy who was born in this land
but was laid to rest in another country.
You're his descendant.
And you look just like him.
Which part, exactly?
Was that ancestor of mine handsome?
Duk Hwa!
I have no idea how such an insolent child
came to be. My apologies, Your Lordship.
Worry not.
You've never disappointed anyone.
But you know, Uncle.
Why do you keep using
informal speech toward Grandpa?
Do you have a death wish
or something?
Why, you little!
Oh my...
Your Lordship.
I offer my deepest apologies
for coming to see you so late.
I've been sick all this
time, Your Lordship.
I must feel the same way
that your blade does, sir.
From this moment on, this child
will serve you, Your Lordship.
This is my grandson.
This sword is "Your Lordship," Grandpa?
It seems that your subjects
have saved your soul.
However, your blade
is stained with blood.
They may have been your enemies,
but they were the gods' creations.
So you will be immortal and alone,
watching your loved ones die before you.
Not a single one of those deaths
will be wiped from your memory.
This blessing is the punishment
that I am giving to you.
And only the Goblin's Bride will be
able to remove that blade.
And when she does, you'll be able to
return to nothingness and rest in peace.
Your Lordship!
There is a place
where I must go.
Who goes there?
How dare you come into
a place like this?
Hey, you insolent...
Y-you... are...
I was too late, it seems.
Grandpa! Grandpa!
Grandpa!
It seems...
that this is the first punishment
that I am receiving.
Please... accept me.
As of this moment,
I will serve you.
That was my grandfather's final wish.
I became blinded
by my desire for revenge...
and couldn't even ask your
grandfather how he'd been.
And yet...
you wish to serve me?
It's quite nice to be able to enjoy
a view like this at my leisure.
And I'm happy that you can enjoy
a view like this at your leisure.
Here.
You should have it, Your Lordship.
I'm still quite full.
How is it that you're full
when you've had nothing to eat?
I'm tiny, so I get full even after
eating the tiniest morsel of food.
You're much bigger than I am, sir,
so please eat that instead.
We can do this, then.
We're still quite
far from land, sir.
Neither of us will be full
if we share this.
So is that why
you're insisting on starving?
I'm a child, so I can go around
to beg for food if I get hungry.
Do you think I brought you with me
just to have you go around begging?
Trust me.
I may be an even greater
person than you imagine.
Come, now.
Wow!
Your Lordship!
Can I peek in that bag of yours?
We need to decrease
the weight on this boat, you see.
Your Lordship.
Your Lordship!
Put that child down now.
If you do, I'll let you keep
your life at the very least.
It's clear there's someone among us who's
at fault for the waves being unruly.
I'll sell you as a slave,
so give me your hands and feet!
And as for this squirt,
throw him overboard.
Do you know what happens to
humans who are lesser than animals?
They meet the God of Wrath.
H-h-he's a goblin!
Please, spare us!
It's too late.
It sure is nice to be back
here at my leisure.
Why? Why did you do that?
If there is a god, please...
please, save me.
Please, save me.
Just anybody, please. Save me!
Who are you?
I'm "just anybody."
Please... please, help me.
Well, I don't know.
It's my rule not to get involved
in human beings' lives.
I... really can't
just die like this.
The one you're asking me
to save isn't you, is it?
Just my child, at least. Please.
You're lucky, though, to have
met a soft-hearted god like me.
It's just that I don't want
to see anyone die tonight.
[JI YEON HEE. 27 YEARS OLD. BORN IN
THE YEAR OF THE TIGER ON MARCH 1ST.]
[NO NAME. ZERO YEARS OLD.]
Snow, and rain, and...
flowers, eh?
- The Goblin's Bride is back.
[EIGHT YEARS LATER]
What do you want for your
birthday this year, Eun Tak?
Round rice cakes?
Square rice cakes?
Mom. Can't I have a party now
instead of Korean-style parties?
What's the difference?
Well, a cake instead of
rice cakes, for one.
I want to blow out candles
and make a wish too.
I think the reason why my
wish isn't coming true is because
I've been making my wishes on rice
cakes instead of birthday candles.
Oh, I didn't realize!
I only got you rice cakes
because you like them!
All right, then. Let's throw you
a party with cake from now on.
Wow! You're the best, Mom!
Oh, it's a puppy!
Huh? A puppy?
Look at this.
It's spring again.
Isn't that fascinating?
Ah, I'm so tired.
Mom, I got a 100 on
my English quiz today!
I'm super-duper tired because
I used so much brainpower today!
Oh, really?
Wow! It's cake!
Are we going to have
a party now, Mom?
Yeah. Come and sit.
Light the candles.
Is it okay for me to light them?
You can do it since you're
all grown up now, Eun Tak.
Oh yeah.
I'm nine years old now.
I even got a 100 on my English
quiz, so this is a cakewalk.
Where did you learn that saying?
You don't need to know, Mom.
I'm just good at picking up these
things from all sorts of people.
I think I might be a genius...
What's the matter?
You have to make a wish.
Happy birthday, my little pup!
It's not really you, Mom.
It's your spirit that
I'm talking to, isn't it?
So... you really can see
everything, can't you?
I was hoping that you
wouldn't be able to.
Are you dead, Mom?
Really?
Where are you, Mom?
Where are you now?
At Sageori Hospital.
You'll be getting
a call from the hospital.
And when you get there,
your aunt will arrive soon.
It's cold at night, so make
sure you have a scarf on.
Ask the granny at the supermarket
to go with you too. Okay?
You know how to get to
her place, right?
Go down the alleyway next to
the dry cleaners and then make a right.
Oh, you're so clever,
my little pup!
Don't ever look another spirit
in the eye from now on, okay?
I'm sorry, Mom, that I can see spirits.
But it's because I can see spirits
that I can see you now.
I'm okay, Mom.
Okay.
Thank you so much...
for seeing me like this.
I... I think that
I have to go now.
I love you, my little pup.
Me too.
I love you too, Mom.
Bye, Mom. Goodbye.
You have to go to heaven, okay?
You have to!
Mom!
Hello? Is this
Ms. Ji Yeon Hee's home?
This is Sageori Jaeil
Hospital, and...
I know.
I'll head over there.
I'm not going to make a wish.
I'm not going to make
even a single wish.
Nobody ever grants
them for me anyway.
So who would I even
make the wish to?
How is it that you never
seem to grow old, Granny?
How could I possibly get
any older than this?
You do have a point.
Can't you check up on my Eun Tak
every once in a while?
Spouting such nonsense again.
Why would I check up
on your daughter?
Just every once in a while!
Give her some leftover
cabbage if you have any
and some spinach, too.
You should've just died then. Why did you
have to ask them to give you more time?
You're so mean.
You're the one who told me
to plead with them with all my heart.
And you actually believed that?
And thanks to that, I got to live
for a bit longer before I had to go.
Thanks for everything, Granny.
I came to say goodbye.
I'm... going now.
Who are you, Mister?
You... can see me?
Oh, my scarf. I didn't put it on.
Mom's going to yell at me.
You have it on already, though.
This is Ms. Ji Yeon Hee's home, right?
I came here since her spirit
wasn't at the hospital.
But how is a child like you, who wasn't
supposed to have been born...
??
Did you, by any chance,
become nine years old this year?
I can't hear your voice
at all, Mister.
What brings you here, ma'am?
Go. And leave this child alone.
Granny!
You're getting in the way of my work.
As if.
Why are you trying to take her now
when it's already been so long?
I'm glad for this chance.
Better late than never.
I have no time right now.
That's your problem.
Do you have this child's
name on your list?
She had no name back then,
but she has a name now.
If you have a certificate with
her name on it, hand it over.
I'll hand her over if you do.
If I'm going to get that, I need to get
nine years' worth of evidence on her.
You, of all people, should know...
I'll be seeing you again, child.
Granny! Mom is...
I know. And we can't
do anything about that.
But you have to live.
You have to move within three days
if you don't want him to find you.
You've looked a God of Death in the
eye, so you can't live here any longer.
He won't be able to
find me if I move?
No, he won't.
That's why land is so important.
After midnight, a man and two women
will come for you at the funeral parlor.
Go with them.
It'll be hard on you,
but you have no other choice.
But why are you telling
me all of this?
Because I've taken a liking to you.
When she was pregnant with you...
she was so happy.
Here. A birthday gift.
[10 YEARS LATER]
Excuse me.
Want to get a drink with me?
Sure.
This card worked up until
yesterday, but now it doesn't!
So, um, Uncle.
There are some unfriendly
guys in suits at the bar.
I'm, um, with those people right now.
So please, pick up the phone!
They asked for your cell phone number
and got really unfriendly when
I told them that you don't have one.
Uncle. Are you listening?
Uncle! Uncle!
Uncle!
She still eats by herself even
though it's the end of senior year.
If you feel that bad for her,
go and eat with her yourself.
Are you crazy?
Why would I do that?
That girl sees spirits!
I'm more scared of her
than I am of ghosts.
At least you can't see ghosts.
Look. She can hear everything we're
saying, but she's acting as if she can't.
Hey.
Hey, I heard that
you're the Goblin's Bride.
Come on, I know you can see me.
Come with me.
It's just that I'm so lonely!
Please?
Hey, why do you keep ignoring me?
You evil girl!
Oh, geez!
See? I knew you could see me.
Wait, so it's true?
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
What was that? Why did she
apologize all of the sudden?
You didn't even turn on
any of the lights, Your Lordship.
I was lost in my thoughts.
These are the materials you
requested of me from the NIS.
Then...
Yes. It's happened, Your Lordship.
Duk Hwa is already 25 years old now.
I've pulled a lot of strings so you can
leave near the end of the month.
If you leave now, Your Lordship...
this will be the last time in
my lifetime I'll see you, correct?
I thank you for every second
that we've shared together.
Duk Hwa will be here
when you return, sir.
I've been losing my keys
all the time lately
so I've had the lock
changed to a keyless one.
Grandpa! Uncle Shin!
There you are, Uncle Shin.
I begged you to come and pick me up.
But here you are.
Do not interrupt an adults' conversation!
Did you cancel my card?
You canceled my card, didn't you!
Yeah, I canceled it, you brat.
Ugh, I was totally humiliated!
Do you know how tough she was to get to?
Why did you even make me your heir
if you were going to treat me like this?
Uncle Shin, are you going somewhere?
- Where are you going?
- I told you to speak with more respect!
Stay out of this, Grandpa.
Is it about that thing again?
About you looking for your bride?
Why can't you just say that you're
leaving to get married somewhere?
Why can't you say it!
You're saying this kid will be here
when I return?
Uncle Shin, exactly when
and what time are you leaving?
One male and two females!
Your breakfast is ready.
I said, your breakfast is ready.
Shut up, you loudmouth.
Why are you blabbering so much over
the stupid breakfast you cooked?
What's with the seaweed soup?
Is it someone's birthday today?
Are you kidding me? Did she make the soup
because it's her birthday or something?
Yeah, it is.
How can she be proud of having killed her
own mom just to be born on this day?
She's shameless because
she doesn't know any better.
Whatever she learned, she got it from you
since she's been with us for 10 years.
Shut up and eat your food.
Thanks for wishing me a happy birthday.
This is why people say that
you should never take in a stray.
Being too compassionate is my downfall.
I'm the pitiful one here since
I've raised her in her mother's stead.
Your words are a bit harsh.
How is it harsh?
She may be your mom,
but she's my older sister.
Exactly. She and I are closer in
both heart and connection.
- Do you even know what you're saying?
- Shut up and eat your food.
Where are you running off to?
I'm not running off anywhere.
I'm going to school.
You're dead if you touch those umbrellas.
Meet me at the bank
with your bankbook after school.
You know what will happen
if you don't, right?
How many times have I told you
that I don't have a bankbook?
Then where's the bankbook?
Where's your mom's insurance money?
How would I know that?
You took all the money for yourself!
You even took the money from our house!
Why is she talking
so much crap this morning?
Just shut up and bring it
unless you want to get your ass beaten.
The bankbook disappears whenever
I need to go to the bank
and who else could it be but you?
I'm telling you that
the bitch is possessed.
That's right.
There's a ghost right behind you.
What! You crazy bitch!
My lordship.
Will you be traveling alone
this time too?
Yes, it would seem so.
No women I've ever met has been
able to see the sword.
Which is of a great relief to me.
I hope the bride appears quickly for you
when you're in agony over the sword.
But if the sword is seen,
I hope no one finds out about it.
That's just human greed, I guess.
It's a relief for me too.
To still have you by my side,
and a full drink in my hand besides.
For tonight at least,
I'd like to remain alive.
Shall we drink to that?
When I was nine years old,
I told myself that I'd never do this.
But I'm desperate right now,
so I hope you understand.
Please help me find a job,
do something about my relatives
and please help me find a boyfriend!
Please help me find a job,
do something about my relatives
and help me improve my pathetic life.
Even 100 won in my pocket
would be fine! Please.
What in the world am I doing?
Who am I even praying to?
There is no god.
You're seriously not going to
make it rain right now, are you?
It's not even the rainy season!
Will the rain even stop?
Will it ever?
Why do you keep making it rain when
I don't even have an umbrella of my own?
- Was it you?
- Oh my goodness.
Me?
- Were you talking to me?
- Yeah, you.
Was it you?
- What about me?
- Were you the one who summoned me?
- Me? I didn't summon you.
- You did summon me.
- But just how did you summon me?
- How would I have summoned you?
- I seriously didn't summon you.
- You definitely did summon me.
- Try to remember how you summoned me.
- Desperately?
I didn't summon you.
I'm just able to see you.
Because we accidentally locked eyes
when we passed each other the other day.
You're him, aren't you?
- What do you mean, you can see me?
- You're a ghost, aren't you?
I'm able to see ghosts.
- I'm not a ghost.
- That's what they all say at first.
Who are you?
Why can't you see what you
should see right in front of you?
- What am I supposed to see?
- Your twenties, thirties... your future.
Maybe because there is no future for me.
Were you a shaman or something
before you died? Or a con man?
- My future, my butt.
- What? A con, what?
Go to the light.
Wandering around for too long isn't good.
- What's with those flowers?
- I thought you wanted me to leave.
Okay, leave.
They're buckwheat flowers.
But that's not what I'm asking.
Why are you holding those flowers?
Give them to me.
They don't really suit you.
I've never been told that before.
I've seriously never been told that.
You can just give them to me.
It's my birthday today.
A very depressing birthday.
I get nothing but weeds for my birthday.
I got a napa cabbage
for my ninth birthday.
But what is the meaning
of these buckwheat flowers?
Lovers.
Why were you crying?
Job, relatives, or boyfriend?
Which of the three were you crying over?
- How did you know that?
- I heard you.
What do you mean, you heard it?
- I grant some people their wishes.
- You grant people their wishes?
Like a magic genie?
Or a guardian angel?
Are you serious?
I knew it.
I knew you were different from other
ghosts from the moment I first saw you.
- Are you really my guardian angel?
- I didn't say I was your guardian angel.
My mom once told me that everyone is born
with their own life dictionary.
And in my dictionary, words such as
"Luck" or "Fortune" don't exist.
- You know what I mean, right?
- No, I don't.
I'm asking if I can have
about five million.
If getting me the cash is too tough,
then tell me the winning lottery numbers.
Go and say goodbye to your family.
You won't get to see them for a while.
Keep looking for a job at a chicken
restaurant. You'll find something soon.
Hey! What about my boyfriend?
Hello? Hey!
Ugh, what a poor sport!
- I haven't met you before.
- Likewise.
But I have heard rumors.
There are all sorts of rumors about me.
What are you doing in my home?
You live here?
All the furniture you see is included,
so you just need to move in...
When did you get home, Uncle Shin?
- Explain.
- The thing is...
this house is going to sit vacant
for like 20 years.
I thought about the money we could make
by charging someone monthly rent...
Do you even know what that is?
That thing over there is...
Don't refer to our new tenant as "that"!
He owns tea houses.
I'm sorry, I apologize.
My uncle is socially awkward.
- Here's your coffee.
- Thanks.
- He hasn't paid yet.
- I saw the new car out front.
- It's the new tenant's car.
- It's not my car.